http://www.rccgb.co.uk/privacy-policy.html

Useful Links
Where have we been?
Useful Links
Where have we been?
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to The Roller Coaster Club of Great Britain and their website. In this privacy policy references to "we", "us" and "our" are to The Roller Coaster Club of Great Britain. References to "website" are to rccgb.co.uk.
Information we collect
We may collect the following information:any personal details you knowingly provide us through forms such as name, address, date of birth etc.contact information including email addressinformation on how you use the website using cookies; this includes the internet browser you use, the site you came to us from and your IP address (See "How we use cookies" below for more information)
What we do with your information
Any personal information we collect will be used in accordance with EU data protection regulations. The information we collect will be used:to administer your membership to The Roller Coaster Club of Great Britainto process any trip applications you submit
Keeping your information secure
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial controls to safeguard and secure the information we collect.
Disclosing your information
We will not share your information with any other organisations for their own marketing, market research or commercial purposes. We may pass on the information we collect about you:if we need to disclose your personal information to any law enforcement agency, court, regulator, government authority where we believe this is necessary to comply with a legal or regulatory obligationto any third party or supplier for the purposes of providing a trip you have applied for where you have provided consent  (i.e. to an airline provider for group flight bookings)
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you.We use cookies on our website:Google Analytics CookiesThese cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. Click here for an overview of privacy at Google. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Other CookiesThe website is built and run on the web based Weebly platform. Weebly use cookies from quantserve.com, editmysite.com and snowplough.com. These cookies are described by Weebly as strictly necessary for the operation of the website. Click here to see Weebly's privacy policy.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Your rights
Under data protection regulations, you have a number of rights. For example, you can ask us:for a copy of the information we hold about youto delete information or correct any inaccuraciesto update any out-of-date informationYou should send your request in writing to the address below with enough information for us to confirm your identity:The Roller Coaster Club of Great BritainPO Box 235UxbridgeMiddlesexUB10 0TF
Links to other websites
Our website contains links to other websites of interest and rccgb.digitickets.co.uk which is used to process online trip bookings, membership and associated payments. Once you have used these links to leave our website, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you may provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy of the website in question which may differ from ours.
Changes to this policy
We occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we change the 'last updated' date at the end of the privacy policy.
Last Updated: 30 December 2017
Home     Media     Contact Us     Privacy© 1988-2020 The Roller Coaster Club of Great BritainPO Box 235, Uxbridge, Middlesex, UB10 0TF.
